[Music]
presenting
icici lombard personal accident cover
this policy protects you with a cover of
up to 10 lakh rupees as well as an
additional 90 000 rupees for taking care
of your parents the policy is
exclusively available to free pay card
members
for a premium of just
699 rupees inclusive of all taxes and
all it takes is three easy steps
simply visit freepayonline.com
enter your details and the activation
code
complete the verification process and
get your policy
it's just that simple
the policy gives you coverage for one
year
and is available to everyone between the
age of 18 and 65 years
and that's not all
the claims process is simple and
seamless and can be initiated via call
email or on our website you can also
track the status of your claim online
so what are you waiting for get the
protection and peace of mind you deserve
with personal accident cover today
icici lombard
nepali
[Music]